(Sheldon:)And I'm not?
(rumbling)
(gasps)
It's an earthquake.
(Sheldon:)I knew it.
(Penny:)Sheldon, it was
just a little tremor.
(Sheldon:)A little tremor that turns
routine sinus surgery
(Sheldon:)into a frontal
lobotomy.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't care
for this at all.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I need to
see he's okay.
(Amy:)Sheldon, you can't
go back there.
Try and stop me!
(thud)
(Amy:)Are you okay?
Why didn't you stop me?!
(Bernadette:)Can I tell you
something?
(Bernadette:)This whole thing
with Raj's parents
(Bernadette:)just got me
a little worried about us.
(Howard:)What are you talking about?
We're fine.
(Howard:)And Raj's parents
(Howard:)probably split up
because of Raj.
What?!
(Howard:)They always say the children
aren't to blame, but...
(laughing):
Come on.
(Bernadette:)I'm not joking, Howie.